

#### **PROFILE**

I have been working in IT for more than 10 years, I always want to learn new technologies and forms of development to implement them at work and that the result is always the best.
I am proactive, I like teamwork and I prioritize a good work environment.
I adapt easily to change.

### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

54-9-11-5693-0187

E-MAIL:

bvma129@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergiomurua/? locale=en\_US

**LANGUAGUE** 

Spanish / English

# SERGIO RUBEN MURUA

Sr FullStack Developer

#### **EDUCATION**

UAI - Systems Engineer (incomplete)

2007 - 2011

**UNGS - Systems Engineer (in course)** 

2020 - At present

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BBVA - Sr Developer

01-2021 - at present

Fullstack developer for internal application. Working in Java from 1.5 to 11, Python. Cloud with GCP. Using DB Oracle, Sybase, Sql Server, Mongo, Mysql.

## Wabi - Sr Developer

12-2019 - 01-2021

Backend developer with Graphql, java8, Kotlin, Groovy, Testing(TDD/BDD) Mockito, junit, Cl/CD, git, all in AWS(Lambda, RDS, Dynamo, s3, SNS, SQS, EC2, CloudFormation), SCRUM. Reactor Programming.

### Neoris - Sr Developer

07-2019 - 12-2019

Sr Developer on Finance department for the most important banks, develop features about internal requirements on Java, Angular, Rest, SCRUM, Testing con TDD/BDD, CI/CD, adaptacion de site en IONIC, React JS

## Cetelem - Web Programmer Analyst

04-2011- 07-2019

Development of new websites and maintenance in Java, PHP, Spring, Angular. Develop ecommerce site. Control Version GIT Development and maintenance of accounting system in JAVA, Springboot, angular and MSSQL.

Support and development of applications in Perl.

Maintenance of applications in .NET. Development of new functionalities in HomeBanking in java architecture design.

Development and implementation of Java applications for Call Center Claims Management facilitating the necessary adaptations for the business. Development on Oracle database, MS SQL, Mysql, optimization and refactoring of pl / sql.

Development of the CALL/CPFIJO system for the accounting department to resolve audit objections of BCRA.

## Clickbed.com - Java Programmer

04-2010 - 04-2011

Development, maintenance and optimization of the web site.

## Vulcano - Perl and PHP Programmer (Freelance)

11-2009-02-2011

Site Development in php for the attention and administration of the Technical Service orders. Development of the e-commerce site in perl. Linux server administration

## Gesfor - Programmer

08-2009-03-2010

Development of internal interface for writing and dealing with news of important agency. Development of testing for code in phpunit.

Arming and configuration of the continuous integration server (CruiseControl).

## Sofrecom - PHP, Perl Programmer

03-2009-08-2009

Development of modules in php with oracle for an interface using ajax and javascript. Development of plugins for radius with perl. Interface generation for the creation of ipv networks Development Java internal site.

## Movilgate - PHP, Perl Programmer

03-2008-03-2009

Creation of web interface for platform management in php5 with mysql (stored procedure, triggers, view, functions) using ajax, smarty, javascript, prototype. Development of sms applications in perl. Creation of web with embedded perl. Development of Web services.

## JetMultimedia – Java, PHP, Perl

Programmer 09-2005-02-2008

Platform migration in java to php with sql server 2000. Refactoring of stored procedure, triggers, functions, views. Development of sms applications with php. Development of plugins for nagios in perl. Maintenance of platform in php. Web development for promotions using ajax, smarty, javascript, prototype. Administration of applications in linux environment. Development of wap platform. Development of Web services. Use of shell scripting (linux)